[{"answer": "Michael Phelps has definitely earned every single one of these 19 medals that he's won thus far.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What does it mean to any Olympic athlete?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "No, it can't be there.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Can it be there when he win eight gold medals?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "We're debating it because of the history of women's swimming.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "It may not be so much of a racial thing.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Would this debate be on front page of newspapers around the world?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think we are.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Are we giving her a bad rap, do you think?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I believe it would.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "ORGAN: Would it happened to an American?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, China paid a huge price for what they did in the 1990s.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Is it not right to at least ask a question?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I: Could it be because China has been performing very well.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Do you think the part of this is because China are beating America, winning more gold medals, but a jealousy maybe?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Are we seeing a real resurgence now do you think in gymnastics for the American team?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "There isn't really.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "ORGAN: What is the nightmare scenario to deal with for you?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "There's a range of capabilities we can put in the back of this aircraft.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "And their job will be to intercept?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "These helicopters could be the fastest rapid response tool that you have on this boat, right?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "In a matter of moments.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "And they can take off how fast?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "This is the OCBP.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "This extraordinary looking beast here, what is it?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "If there was a major incident down at the Olympics, you could get here pretty quickly from here, right?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "You guys are basically armed to the teeth and ready if you need to be, aren't you?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "HMS Ocean is the royal Navy's largest ship.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What's the difference in terms of what you do as the captain?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Very much so.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "And would you say from all your experience that we're ready?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "At the moment we've got just over a thousand people on board.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "I mean how much food are you serving a day for these guys?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I've often said that anyone who's done bobsleigh, especially as a driver, if they weren't scared once during their career, they weren't real bobsledders.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Is it as terrifying to do it?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "We have six athletes.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "How many -- there are six I heard?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I'm always optimistic about South Africa.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What would you feel about South Africa today?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes, I met him at the United Nations a couple of years ago.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What do you think of him?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, I think America -- we still look up to America in many ways.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "I don't know about that as yet.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Does that go for your children too?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "First of all, I can't believe it's already 30 years since her passing.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "What do you think she would have made of the way that you have conducted yourself since you had to take over the reins of the palace?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "She was the most warm, gracious, engaging person.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "But for those who didn't know your mother, how would you describe her?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I never actually had a passport, but I had a paper in my passport that said when I was to travel to the United States, I shouldn't be considered as a foreign citizen.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Do you have any American citizenship because of your mother?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Very well, thank you.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "How's it going, Princess Charlene?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Busy.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Life is good as Princess Charlene?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, from what I've experienced, it's very busy, a lot of responsibilities.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What is the reality of entering a royal family?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I get to wear a tiara now and then.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Other than being married to this charming, handsome prince?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I wanted to be Zoro.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "did you ever think, one day I want to be a princess, marry a handsome prince?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "There is an upside.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Well, it's not true, is it?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "RINCESS CHARLENE: Well, training in South Africa, I was, you know often training alongside athletes that had disabilities and, you know, they also tried to get to their meets, to reach their goals in life, very little support.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't say expensive or inexpensive.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How do you view it?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Piers, it's a great question.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "As one of the main sponsors, how do you feel about what NBC is doing, which is basically ignoring the rally cry to be airing the big events live and they're sticking to their prime-time schedule?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I don't think there's a very simple answer for all of that.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "What do you think about the -- people like I guess Starbucks for example opening factories back in America at a bit of a loss leader, but doing it to make a point, we want to bring jobs back to America?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "They ought to take a look at -- they ought to understand, business is not the enemy.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Whoever wins in November, what should they do about that?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I would have to say we would consider it.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "If they made it more attractive for businesses like yours to bring factories back to America, would you do that?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Not running, that's why I row.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "You've been quicker in your career, haven't you?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I think it probably was being asked to do it in the first place.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Was it receiving it from the great Becks?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "It is the biggest sporting event there is.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "What is it about the Olympics that makes great champions keep coming back, do you think?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "I think, going back, it would probably be when I was a 10- year-old, of watching Mark Spitz win his seventh.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Who is your favorite Olympian in the world, ever?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "I think most people do.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Do you think people have any real understanding of the sacrifice and the dedication that it takes to be the best when you come to the Olympics?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "It would have to be the medals.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "If I case say you could have only one of those, which would you take?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "I've been out in a boat five times this year.", "docId": "120731pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you still row?", "qSentId": 690}]